[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the characteristics below is typical for the buildings on the Greek archipelago of Santorini?", "correct_answer": "The white-and-blue colouring", "incorrect_answers": ["The huge balconies", "The red-tiled roofs", "The arched doors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Pedro felt sickly and hot, what did he do after he got home?", "correct_answer": "He shaved his head.", "incorrect_answers": ["He took some Tylenol.", "He asked his mom for advice.", "He went to bed and slept it off."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The spikes on the tail of a Stegosaurus are called \u201cthagomizers\u201d and are a reference to the Gary Larsons comic strip Far Side.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Fast Times at Ridgemont High, Ridgemont played against which rival football team?", "correct_answer": "Lincoln High", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamilton High", "Clairemont High", "San Fernando Valley High"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the title role in Gunga Din, the 1939 movie based on the Rudyard Kipling poem?", "correct_answer": "Sam Jaffe", "incorrect_answers": ["Eduardo Ciannelli", "Cary Grant", "Douglas Fairbanks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most cultures have a solar diety, someone who represents the Sun.  Who is the chief solar diety in Hinduism?", "correct_answer": "Surya", "incorrect_answers": ["Krishna", "Brahman", "Ishvara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the last juror to vote not  guilty in the 1957 movie Twelve Angry Men?", "correct_answer": "Lee J. Cobb", "incorrect_answers": ["Ed Begley", "Martin Balsam", "Ed Begley,Jr."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the location of the largest mall in Europe.", "correct_answer": "Istanbul, Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Lyon, France", "Barcelona, Spain", "Moscow, Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which vitamin is the orange pigment beta-carotene converted to by the human body?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin A", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin C", "Vitamin B12", "Vitamin E"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film is a 2009 remake of the 2003 South Korean movie A Tale of Two Sisters.", "correct_answer": "The Uninvited", "incorrect_answers": ["Pulse", "The Last House on the Left", "Mirrors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "George Taliaferro was the second black player ever to be drafted in the NFL.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the first names of the comedy team of Abbot and Costello?", "correct_answer": "Bud and Lou", "incorrect_answers": ["Abbot and Bob", "Dean and Jerry", "Bob and Ray"]}]